Guide to the Yale University Press Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1909-2004; 1976-2004; Accession 2013-A-079
  - Publication Committee meeting files
    - 1976 December 13 (Box 9, Folder 264)
    - 1978 January 23 (Box 9, Folder 265)
    - 1978 February 13 (Box 9, Folder 266)
    - 1978 March 6 (Box 9, Folder 267)
    - 1978 April 10 (Box 9, Folder 268)
    - 1978 May 8 (Box 9, Folder 269)
    - 1978 June 19 (Box 9, Folder 270)
    - 1978 September 18 (Box 10, Folder 271)
    - 1978 October 9 (Box 10, Folder 272)
    - 1978 November 20 (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - 1978 December 11 (Box 10, Folder 274)
    - 1980 January 14 (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - 1980 February 18 (Box 10, Folder 276)
    - 1980 March 10 (Box 10, Folder 277)
    - 1980 April 14 (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - 1980 May 20 (Box 10, Folder 279)
    - 1980 June 16 (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - 1980 September 15 (Box 10, Folder 281)
    - 1980 October 13 (Box 10, Folder 282)
    - 1980 November 17 (Box 10, Folder 283)
    - 1980 December 15 (Box 10, Folder 284)
    - 1981 January 19 (Box 10, Folder 285)
    - 1981 February 23 (Box 10, Folder 286)
    - 1981 March 23 (Box 10, Folder 287)
    - 1981 April 20 (Box 10, Folder 288)
    - 1981 May 18 (Box 10, Folder 289)
    - 1981 June 15 (Box 10, Folder 290)
    - 1981 September 9 (Box 10, Folder 291)
    - 1981 October 12 (Box 10, Folder 292)
    - 1981 November 9 (Box 10, Folder 293)
    - 1981 December 7 (Box 11, Folder 294)
    - 1982 January 18 (Box 11, Folder 295)
    - 1982 February 22 (Box 11, Folder 296)
    - 1982 March 22 (Box 11, Folder 297)
    - 1982 April 19 (Box 11, Folder 298)
    - 1982 May 17 (Box 11, Folder 299)
    - 1982 June 14 (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - Royalty ledgers
    - A-MO, 1927-1959 (Box 12, Folder 301-304)
    - A-F, 1940-1960 (Box 12, Folder 305-306)
    - CO-HAR, 1927-1959 (Box 13, Folder 307-310)
    - N-Z, 1927-1959 (Box 14, Folder 311-314)
    - N-Z, 1939-1960 (Box 14, Folder 315-316)
    - W-Series, 1927-1955 (Box 15, Folder 317-321)
- Records, 2001-2014; Accession 2014-A-076
  Restricted until January 1, 2049
  - Board of Governor meetings
    - Minutes only, 2001 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Minutes only, 2002 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Minutes only, 2002 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Minutes only, 2002 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 2003 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 2003 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 2004 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 2004 June 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 2004 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 2005 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 2005 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 2005 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 2006 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 2006 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 2006 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 2007 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 2007 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 2007 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 2008 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 2008 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 2008 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 2009 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Incomplete Board of Governor meeting records, 2010 March 26-2011 March 18 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 2011 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 2011 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Committees
    - Finance committee
      - Anchor Bible, 2005 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - 2007 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Publications committee minutes, 2002-2011 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Operating budget
    - FY 2006 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - FY 2013 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Strategic and Five-Year plans
    - FY 2005-2009, 2005 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - FY 2009-2011, 2008 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - FY 2009-2013, 2008 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - FY 2012-2014, 2011 March 10 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Cultural and Civilization of China project records, 1993-2012; Accession 2018-A-024
  Restricted until January 1, 2048
  - Expense/Financial Reports
    - Launch Expenses, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Expense Report, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Checks/Check Req., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Budget/Spending, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Financial Summary, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Launch Planning and Corres., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Meeting Minutes/Memos, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Levin China Visit, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - February-March 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - July-August 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - September 2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - October 2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - November 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Financial Correspondence, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Materials Sent to Huang YouYi, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - January-February 2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - March-May 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - June-July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - CIPG Visit, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Meeting Agendas, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - General 2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Financial Correspondence 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - China International Publishing Co., 2012 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Beijing Trip DVD, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Biographies, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Classics of Chinese Thought Trans., 2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Classics Letter, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Companion to Classic Chinese Lit., 2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Memos and Corresp., 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Prospects and Programs, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Protocol, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Quality Solutions, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Science Projects, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Travel Expenses, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Travel Schedules, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Support Groups and Advisory Council
    - Levin, Richard, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Info on Members, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Peck, James, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Reed, Jospeh Verner, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Ryden, John, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Published book files, 1986-2017; Accession 2018-A-0040
  Restricted until January 1, 2053
  - Abboud/No More Joint Pain, 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abrams and Primack/The New Universe and the Human Future, 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abromowicz/Preditocracy, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abromowicz/Morandi: The Art of Silence, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Ackerman/Bush vs. Gore, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ackerman/Before the Next Attack, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams/Gouverneur Morris, 1998-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Addition to Bailey/Bedouin, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adonis/Selected Poems, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adnopoz et. al/In Home Care, 2002-2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adorno/The Polemics of Possession in Spanish-American Narrative, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Aitken/Intelligence Tradition, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Akinsha/Holy Place, 1999-2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alarco and Warner/Mirror and the Mask, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Albanese/Republic Mind and Spirit, 1995-2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Agee and Faxon/Coming of Age, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Albers/Poems and Drawings, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Albers/Interaction of Color Pb, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Albers/Interaction of Color-New Complete, 1996-2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Albertson/Bessie, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Allard/Out of Reach: Place, Poverty, and the New American Welfare State, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Allen/The Republic, 1996-2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Allen/Paul Mellon's Legacy, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ali/The Treasure Impulse, 2008-2010 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Allitt/The Conservatives, 2003-2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alter/Imagined Cities, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Anders/Between Fire and Sleep, 2001-2009 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Andersen/This Fine Piece of Winter, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Anderson/Sin: A History, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Anderson/Poem Without A Hero vol. 1, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Anderson/Poem Without A Hero vol. 2, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Anderson/Dr. Dolittle's Delusion, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Andrews/Managing the Environment, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Andrews and Beardsley/Maya Lin, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Anksy/The Dybbuk and Other Writings, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Antognazza/Trinity and Incarnation, 2001-2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Antonova/Masterworks of French Printing, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Artundo/Xul Solar, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Applebaum/Gulag Voices, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Aron/Roads to the Temple, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Askins/Restoring North America's Birds: Second Edition, 1998-2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ashford and Hall/Technology Globalization and Sustainable Development, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Attridge/The Religion and Science Debate: Why Does it Continue?, 2006-2009 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Attenborough et. al/Amazing Rare Things: The Art of Natural History in the Age of Discovery, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ault/Wolfgang Tillmans, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Auner/The Schoenberg Reader, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Averroes/Long Commentary on the De Anima of Aristotle, 1987-2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Avishai/the Great American F-Up, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ayala/Lamb's Head, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Ayres and Klass/Insincere Promises: The Law of Misrepresented Intent, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Axsom/Drawn From Nature, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bagley/Spy Wars: Moles, Mysteries, and Deadly Games, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Baker/Socrates Sculpture Park, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Baker/The Lightning Field, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Balken/After Many Springs, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Banac/Diary of Dimitrov, 1992-2006 (Box 3, Folder 20-22)
  - Balken/John Marin: A Survey of Late Work, 2008-2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Balmori/Constructing Nature, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Baltzell/The Protestant Establishment, 1986-1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Banfield/Jerome Kern, 2000-2006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Banfield/Jerome Kern-Permissions, 2005-2007 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Banta/One True Theory and the Quest For an American Aesthetic, 2005-2007 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Barberie/Looking for Atget, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Barrett/Livia: First Lady of Imperial Rome, 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Barringer/Men at Work, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Barron et. al/Contesting Development: Participatory Projects and Local Conflict Dynamics in Indonesia, 2006-2010 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Barthes/What is Sport?, 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Barton/Wild North America, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bartram/Futurist Typography and the Liberated Text, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Basbanes/A World of Letters, 1993-2008 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Basker/Amazing Grace, 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
  - Bauer/Death of Shtetl, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bedford/Mark Bradford: Against Abstraction, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Barnard and St. James/Listen. Write. Present., 2009-2010 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Baskett/Horse in Art, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Baumgarten/What Clothes Reveal, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Baumol et. al/Good Capitalism, Bad Capitalism and the Economics of Growth and Prosperity, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bayles/The Ugly Americans, 2006-2015 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Beattie/Wild Solutions, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Beaudry/Findings: The Material Culture of Needlework, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Beehler/Lost Worlds: Adventures in the Tropical Rainforest, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Beehler and Ripley/Birds of the Indian Subcontinent, 1991-1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Beekman/Ambonese Herbals, 2004-2012 (Box 5, Folder 8-11)
  - Beekman/Rumphius' Orchids, 1995-2004 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
  - Begley/Why the Dreyfus Affair Matters, 2008-2010 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
  - Beiner and Booth/The Starry Heavens and the Moral Law, 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Belasco/Between the Wares, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Belasco/Contemporary Judaica, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Belknap/The List: Its Pleasures and Uses in 19th Century American Literature, 2001-2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bell/Shakespeare's Tragic Skepticism, 1999-2004 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bell and Sinclair/Pictures and Words, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bellos/Hocus Bogus, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Benedict/Christ's Churches Purely Reformed, 1999-2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Benjamin/Renoir and Algeria, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bentham/Selected Works: Re-Thinking the Western Tradition, 2000-2010 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bennison/The Great Caliphs, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bentley/Sisters of Salome, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
  - Berebitsky/Sex and the Office, 2003-2011 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Berger/For All the World to See, 2005-2010 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Berger/For All the World to See-Permissions, 2006-2009 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Bergelson/The End of Everything, 2004-2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bervin/Olmec: Colossal Masterworks of Ancient Mexico, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Berman/Notes From the Pianists' Bench, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Berman/Prokofiev's Piano Sonatas, 2004-2008 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Berrizbeita/Michael Van Valkenburgh Associates: Reconstructing Urban Landscapes, 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Berra et. al/Heart Attack!, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Berrett/Two Kings of Jazz, 1994-2006 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Berzock/African Ceramics, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bierregard/Lessons From Amazonia, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bill/George Ball, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Billington/Structural Art and the Educated Eye, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bilski and Braun/Jewish Women and Their Salons, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Blackwell/20th Century Type, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Blair/Too Much to Know, 2001-2010 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Blake/Whitman: The Culture of America, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Block et. al/Charles Ives and the Classical Tradition, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Blocker/The Robert Shaw Reader, 2000-2005 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Blokland/Modernization and Its Political Consequences, 2002-2007 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bloom/Fallen Angels, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Bloom and Blair/Islam: 1000 Years of Faith and Power, 2001-2017 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Blum/Shocking! The Art and Fashion of Elsa Schiaparelli, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Bluestein/Clouds: Sculptures in the Sky, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Bockstoce/Furs and Frontiers in the Far North, 2007-2009 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Bogle/The Battle for the Soul of Capitalism, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Bolitho/Bereavement and Consolation, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Bokina/Images of Spartacus, 1998-2008 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Bolman/Monastic Visions, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Bonami/Rudolf Stingel, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Boone/Vistas de Espana, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Boorsch/Master Drawings from the Yale University Art Gallery, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Booth/Shakespeare's Sonnets, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Borchardt-Hume/Albers and Moholy-Nagy: From the Bauhaus to the New World, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Borchardt/Cosmos (Transcription), 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bordes/Jacques-Louis David: Empire to Exile, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Borra and Pausini/Italian Through Film, 2003-2005 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Boroff/Essays, Chiefly Medieval, 1998-2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Boroff/Stars and Other Signs, 2001-2008 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Borzecki/The Soviet-Polish Peace of 1921 and the Creation of Interwar Europe, 2005-2009 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Boswell/Life of Johnson, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Boswell/London Journal, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Bower/From Court to Caravan, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Bowron/Best in Show: The Dog in Art, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Boyajian and Rutoski/Stuart Davis: A Catalogue Raisonne, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
  - Boyle/The Public Domain, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Bradley and Dubois/The Yale Anthology of Rap, 2004-2007 (Box 9, Folder 1-11)
  - Brack/Samuel Johnson vol. 17, 2000-2005 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Bradshaw/Elephants on the Edge, 2007-2009 (Box 9, Folder 13-15)
  - Bradley/Ralph-Ellison-In-Progress, 2008-2010 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Brandt/Deliquency, Development and Social Policy, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Brands/The Strange Death of Liberalism, 2000-2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Braunstein/The Hanukkah Lamps, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Bray/Wetware, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Bremer/Building a New Jerusalem, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Bremer/Chairman of the Fed, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - Brewer and McKay/Wrens, Dippers, and Thrashers, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Brewin/Post Traumatic Stress Disorder, 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Breznitz/Innovation and the State, 2006-2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Breznitz/Run of the Red Queen: Government, Innovation, Globalization and Economic Growth in China, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Bright/Wild Caribbean: The Hidden Wonders of the Worlds Most Famous Islands, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Brockway/Science and Colonial Expansion, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Brodhead/The Good of This Place, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Brodo/Lichens of North America, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Brogan/Alexis de Tocqueville, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Brooks/Realist Visions, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
  - Brown/Culture, Capitalism, and Democracy in the New America, 1995-2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Brown/Full Bodies, 2003-2009 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Brown/Letters from America, 2008-2009 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Brown/A Portrait of Mendelssohn, 1993-2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Brown/Renaissance of Venetian Painting, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Brown/Unfocused Mind, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
  - Broyles/Mavericks and Other Traditions, 1993-2004 (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
  - Brunner/Moon: A Brief History, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Brunetta and Craig/Spider Silk, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Brunner/Finding Common Ground, 1998-2002 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Brunetti/An Anthology of Graphic Fiction, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
  - Brunetti/An Anthology of Graphic Fiction vol. 2, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Brunetti/Cartooning: Philosophy and Practice, 2010-2011 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Brunner/Bears: A Brief History, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bruno/The Cabala of Pegasus, 1999-2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Brush/Farmer's Bounty, 2001-2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Brustein/Millenial Stages, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Brustein/Tainted Muse, 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Bruzina/Edmund Husserl, 1996-2005 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - Bryant/Nongovernment Organizations in Environmental Struggles, 1999-2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Bulgakov/White Guard, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Burke/Reflections on the Revolutions in France, 1998-2003 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Burney/Poor Man's Time Machine, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Burrow/A History of the Yale School of Medicine, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Burt/Marshes: The Disappearing Edens, 2005-2007 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Butler/Hidden in the Shadow of the Master, 2007-2009 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Butler/My Dear Mr. Stalin, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Cabares/August 1914: France Goes to War, 2014-2016 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cahill/Household and City Organization at Olynthus, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Calabresi and Yoo/A History of the Unitary Executive, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Calder/The New Continentalism, 2010-2012 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Callahan/The Talking Book, 2004-2006 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - Campanella/The Republic of Shade, 1999-2003 (Box 13, Folder 8-9)
  - Campbell/Echos: Cultural Discussions for Students of French, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
  - Campbell/Henry VIII and the Art of Majesty, 2006-2007 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Cantwell and Wall/Touring Gotham's Archaeological Past, 2001-2004 (Box 13, Folder 13-15)
  - Capretz/French in Action parts 1 and 2, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Carboni/Venice and the Islamic World, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Carcopino/Daily Life in Ancient Rome, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Carlano/Vernacular Visionaries, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
  - Carlin/Masters of American Comics, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Carmichael/Sex and the Bible, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Carroll/Engaging the Moving Image, 2001-2004 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Carter/The Memoirs of Ernest A. Forssgren, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Carter/Jean Faultrier, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Carter/Oklahoma!, 2003-2007 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Carter/Proust in Love, 2003-2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cash/John Wilkes: The Scandalous Father of Civil Liberty, 2004-2007 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Cashore/Governing Through Markets, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Cavanagh/Lyric Poetry and Modern Politics, 1994-2009 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Caws/Yale Anthology of 20th Century French Poetry, 2000-2005 (Box 14, Folder 7-13)
  - Cesarini/Disraeli, 2015-2016 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Chafetz/Democracy's Privileged Few, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Chanda/Bound Together, 2003-2007 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Chang/Falun Gong: The End of Days, 2000-2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chang et. al/The Formation of Chinese Civilization, 2001-2005 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Changeaux/The Good, the True, and the Beautiful, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Chantler/Swifts: A Guide to the Swifts and Treeswifts of the World, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Culture and Civilizations (Series), 1998-2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Chapman/Michelangelo Drawings: Closer to the Master, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Charlesworth/The Good and Evil Serpent, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
  - Chase and Chase/An Introduction to Spanish for Heath Care Workers, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Chapuis/Tilman Riemenschneider, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Cheke and Hume/Lost Land of the Dodo, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Chen/Juvenalia, 2008-2010 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Cheng/Designing Type, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Chevlowe/The Jewish Identity Project, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Cheroux/The Perfect Medium, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Christensen/Patient Adherence to Medical Treatment Regimens, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Chukovskaya/The Diary of Kornei Chukovsky, 1992-1997 (Box 15, Folder 19-21)
  - Chyet/Kurdish-English Dictionary, 1999-2003 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
  - Cienciala/Katyn: A Crime Without Punnishment, 1997-2008 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Citron/Jerry Herman: Poet of the Showtune, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
  - Clark/The Policy of Progress, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Clark and Dobrenko/Soviet Culture and Power, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  - Clarke-Stewart and Bretano/Divorce: Causes and Consequences, 2001-2007 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Clarke/Dwelling Place, 2004-2006 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Clark/Finding a Path Toward Sustainability, 2005-2008 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Clifton and Scattone/Plains of Mars, 2006-2008 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Clyde and Delohery/Technology in the Classroom, 2001-2005 (Box 16, Folder 12-13)
  - Codrington/Kyle Cooper, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Cogeval/Edouard Vuillard, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Cohen/Life with Others, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Cohen/Notes from the Ground, 2006-2009 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Cohn/Orswell Collection, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Coleman/Vicious: Wolves and Men in America, 2002-2005 (Box 16, Folder 19-20)
  - Colinvaux/Amazon Expeditions, 2009-2011 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Colley/Principles of General Management, 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 2)